Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪Time rushes by, seasons change, autumn winds bring melancholy♪
♪يمر الوقت بسرعة، وتتغير الفصول، وتجلب رياح الخريف الكآبة♪
♪Scattered fragments can't piece together the memories of the past♪
♪الشظايا المتناثرة لا يمكنها تجميع ذكريات الماضي♪
♪The movie hasn't ended, tears glimmer in my eyes♪
♪الفيلم لم ينتهي بعد، والدموع تتلألأ في عيني♪
♪Sitting alone by the street, feeling lost and hesitant♪
♪أجلس وحدي في الشارع، أشعر بالضياع والتردد♪
♪Under the sycamore, let it drift, let it dance♪
♪تحت شجرة الجميز، دعها تنجرف، دعها ترقص♪
♪Whispering softly♪
♪همس بهدوء♪
♪The flowers that withered in my hand♪
♪الزهور التي ذبلت في يدي♪
♪Cannot call back the ones gone♪
♪لا أستطيع استدعاء من رحلوا♪
♪Under the sycamore, let it shatter, let it fade away♪
♪تحت شجرة الجميز، دعها تتحطم، دعها تتلاشى♪
♪Old stories like drifting dust♪
♪قصص قديمة مثل الغبار المنجرف♪
♪Letters too short for my long feelings, youth slips away♪
♪رسائل قصيرة جدًا بالنسبة لمشاعري الطويلة، الشباب يتلاشى♪
♪Farewell, my dear♪
♪ وداعا يا عزيزي ♪
♪Endless pain through day and night cycles♪
♪ألم لا ينتهي خلال دورات الليل والنهار♪
♪Longing and care♪
♪الشوق والرعاية♪
=Life Like=
=مثل الحياة=
=Episode 4=
=الحلقة 4=
How do you know I got shot
كيف عرفت أنني أصبت برصاصة؟
because of Du Hongyue?
بسبب دو هونغيو؟
It's Liu.
إنه ليو.
Liu told me.
قال لي ليو.
Why would Liu tell you that?
لماذا قال لك ليو ذلك؟
That's what he told me.
هذا ما قاله لي.
Believe it or not.
صدق أو لا تصدق.
Hey.
يا.
Who leaked the news?
من سرب الخبر؟
Everyone's been contained?
هل تم احتواء الجميع؟
Handed over to Man Li.
تم تسليمه إلى مان لي.
Please spare us.
من فضلك انقذنا.
We didn't betray you.
نحن لم نخونك
It wasn't us!
لم نكن نحن!
Betray the Chamber,
خيانة الغرفة،
and this is what you get.
وهذا ما تحصل عليه.
Your aim's getting better and better.
هدفك أصبح أفضل وأفضل.
No wonder you're our Chamber's sharpshooter.
لا عجب أنك قناص غرفتنا.
Of course.
بالطبع.
Thanks to your guidance.
شكرا لتوجيهاتكم.
What's it got to do with me?
ما علاقة هذا بي؟
Bad luck.
سوء الحظ.
Zhou Musheng, new at the liaison office,
تشو موشينغ، جديد في مكتب الاتصال،
took a bullet for me during a deal.
لقد تلقيت رصاصة من أجلي أثناء صفقة.
He's still in the hospital.
مازال في المستشفى.
Zhou Musheng?
تشو موشينغ؟
From Nanpu School?
من مدرسة نانبو؟
Yes.
نعم.
I used to teach him at Nanpu School.
كنت أعلمه في مدرسة نانبو.
He's your senior, in a way.
إنه أكبر منك سنا، بطريقة ما.
I remember him.
انا أتذكره.
He was a star at our school.
لقد كان نجمًا في مدرستنا.
Two years above me.
سنتين فوقي.
Since you know each other,
بما أنكما تعرفان بعضكما البعض،
come with me,
تعال معي،
let's visit him in the hospital.
دعونا نزوره في المستشفى.
How's his injury?
كيف حال إصابته؟
Is his life in danger?
هل حياته في خطر؟
Why do you care so much?
لماذا تهتم بهذا القدر؟
It's normal to care for a fellow schoolmate.
من الطبيعي أن تهتم بزميلك في المدرسة.
You talk too much.
تتكلم كثيرا
Look at her!
أنظر إليها!
She snaps at me every time.
إنها تهاجمني في كل مرة.
You
أنت
don't start trouble.
لا تبدأ المشاكل.
Don't provoke our Miss.
لا تستفز سيدتنا.
Or you'll get scolded.
أو سوف يتم توبيخك.
Boss.
رئيس.
You're so obviously biased!
من الواضح أنك متحيز جدًا!
Hey, Boss!
مرحبا يا رئيس!
So, are we going to the hospital?
إذن هل سنذهب إلى المستشفى؟
Of course we're going.
بالطبع نحن ذاهبون.
If not the hospital, where else?
إذا لم يكن المستشفى، أين أيضًا؟
Quit it, or we'll end up in a ditch!
أتركها وإلا سننتهي في خندق!
Musheng.
موشينج.
Feeling better?
هل تشعر بتحسن؟
Much better, sir.
أفضل بكثير يا سيدي.
Senior. Do you still remember me?
كبير السن، هل مازلت تتذكرني؟
Man Li.
مان لي.
You...
أنت...
Man Li
مان لي
is a key member of our Chamber.
هو عضو رئيسي في غرفتنا.
You're her senior.
أنت أكبر منها سنا.
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدا،
take good care of her.
اعتني بها جيدا.
So, Man Li
إذن يا مان لي
is with you too, sir?
هل هو معك أيضا يا سيدي؟
Then from now on,
ومن الآن فصاعدا،
please be patient with me.
من فضلك كن صبورا معي.
Hey,
يا،
enough already.
كفى بالفعل.
He's still injured.
مازال مصابا.
Get well soon.
نتمنى لك الشفاء العاجل.
Thank you, Yao.
شكرا لك يا ياو.
Sir.
سيد.
The doctor said
قال الطبيب
I'm almost fully recovered.
لقد تعافيت تقريبًا بشكل كامل.
After a few days' rest at home,
بعد بضعة أيام من الراحة في المنزل،
I can return to work.
أستطيع العودة إلى العمل.
Rest a few more days at home.
الراحة لبضعة أيام أخرى في المنزل.
When you're fully recovered,
عندما تتعافى بشكل كامل،
come back to work.
العودة إلى العمل.
Senior.
كبير.
When you're recovered,
عندما تتعافى،
I'll come visit you at home.
سأأتي لزيارتك في المنزل.
No need, that's too much trouble.
لا داعي لذلك، فهذا يسبب الكثير من المتاعب.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Get some rest.
احصل على بعض الراحة.
We'll take our leave now.
سوف نأخذ إجازتنا الآن.
Okay, sir.
حسنًا سيدي.
Musheng.
موشينج.
Have an orange.
خذ برتقالة.
Hey.
يا.
You sly fox.
أيها الثعلب الماكر.
Using five scoundrels as scapegoats.
استخدام خمسة من الأشرار ككبش فداء.
Killing two birds with one stone.
قتل عصفورين بحجر واحد.
Sometimes you need a villain's way
في بعض الأحيان تحتاج إلى طريقة الشرير
to beat a villain.
للتغلب على الشرير.
Impressive.
بديع.
Thanks for the compliment.
شكرا على الثناء.
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
how's
كيف الحال
Zhou Musheng doing?
ماذا يفعل تشو موشينغ؟
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
He's discharged and home now.
لقد خرج من المستشفى وعاد إلى منزله الآن.
Good to hear.
يسعدني سماع ذلك.
Who is it?
من هذا؟
Came to see if you're dead yet.
جئت لأرى إذا كنت قد مت بعد.
So vicious for someone so young.
شرير جدًا لشخص صغير السن جدًا.
If I died,
إذا مت
would you inherit my fortune?
هل ترث ثروتي؟
How's your wound?
كيف حال جرحك؟
So impatient?
هل هذا هو الصبر؟
I'm a decent man.
أنا رجل محترم.
Not into daytime indecency.
لا أحب الفحش في النهار.
What are you thinking about?
ماذا تفكر فيه؟
No wonder.
لا عجب.
You got yourself shot.
لقد أطلقت النار على نفسك.
See?
يرى؟
A woman's heart is the cruelest.
قلب المرأة هو الأكثر قسوة.
I'll do it myself.
سأفعل ذلك بنفسي.
Let me.
دعني.
♪Chimes echo through the alleys worn by time♪
♪تتردد الأجراس في الأزقة التي تآكلها الزمن♪
♪Flickering fireflies surround your deep face♪
♪ اليراعات المتلألئة تحيط بوجهك العميق ♪
♪I hold fresh flowers, you hum softly♪
♪أحمل الزهور الطازجة، أنت تدندن بهدوء♪
♪Melodious dance steps, love ripples♪
♪خطوات رقص لحنية، تموجات الحب♪
♪Time rushes by, seasons change, autumn winds bring melancholy♪
♪يمر الوقت بسرعة، وتتغير الفصول، وتجلب رياح الخريف الكآبة♪
Why are you staring at me?
لماذا تحدق بي؟
Is there something on my face?
هل هناك شيء على وجهي؟
A little attractive, maybe.
ربما يكون جذابا بعض الشيء.
Why are you so greasy?
لماذا أنت دهنية جدا؟
♪I can no longer hear your reply♪
♪لم أعد أستطيع سماع ردك♪
♪Farewell, my dear♪
♪ وداعا يا عزيزي ♪
Ouch!
آخ!
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Look at this.
أنظر إلى هذا.
Check this spot.
تحقق من هذا المكان.
Is it broken?
هل هو مكسور؟
Where?
أين؟
Here.
هنا.
Oh my god.
يا إلهي.
Did I come too late?
هل جئت متأخرا؟
Your wound has already healed.
لقد تم شفاء جرحك بالفعل.
Hey!
يا!
It hurts here.
انها تؤلمني هنا .
Hard to move.
من الصعب التحرك.
Help me scrape it.
ساعدني على كشطه.
Too far.
بعيد جداً.
Dangerous.
خطير.
Closer.
أقرب.
A bit closer.
أقرب قليلا.
I can't take it anymore.
لا أستطيع أن أتحمل ذلك بعد الآن.
Quick, help me out.
سريعًا، ساعدني.
(If I hadn't accidentally hurt you,)
(لو لم أؤذيك عن طريق الخطأ)
(I'd really beat you up.)
(سوف أضربك حقا.)
Senior.
كبير.
How's your recovery?
كيف حال تعافيك؟
Man Li.
مان لي.
Why are you here?
لماذا انت هنا؟
I made chicken soup just for you.
لقد صنعت حساء الدجاج خصيصًا لك.
Hey, you there.
مرحباً، أنت هناك.
Go serve the soup.
اذهب لتقديم الحساء.
Thanks for your trouble.
شكرا على تعبك.
Oh, it's
اوه، إنه
that famous little devil from Night Shanghai.
هذا الشيطان الصغير الشهير من ليلة شنغهاي.
Why is she here?
لماذا هي هنا؟
I'm Musheng's woman.
أنا امرأة موشينغ.
Musheng is sick,
موشينغ مريض
of course I have to take care of him.
بالطبع يجب علي أن أعتني به.
Yo.
هم.
Senior.
كبير.
This is your woman?
هذه امرأتك؟
This Night Shanghai girl
هذه الفتاة الليلية في شنغهاي
is yours today.
هو لك اليوم.
Tomorrow,
غداً،
who knows whose she'll be?
من يعلم من ستكون؟
Don't listen to her nonsense.
لا تستمع إلى هراءها.
Come.
يأتي.
Dalang, take your medicine.
دالانغ، خذ دوائك.
- I'll do it.
- سأفعل ذلك.
Let go.
اتركه.
Hot!
حار!
I...
أنا...
I'll get a towel!
سأحضر منشفة!
Here.
هنا.
I'll wipe it for you.
سأمسحها لك.
I'll do it.
سأفعل ذلك.
I'll wipe it.
سأمسحه.
- I'll do it.
- سأفعل ذلك.
Or
أو
should I do it instead?
هل يجب علي أن أفعل ذلك بدلا من ذلك؟
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Senior.
كبير.
Your wound's healed,
لقد تم شفاء جرحك
better head back to the Chamber.
من الأفضل العودة إلى الغرفة.
Take care.
يعتني.
Why is
لماذا هو
Rose here?
وردة هنا؟
That girl is amazing.
تلك الفتاة مذهلة.
When she first came to Night Shanghai,
عندما جاءت لأول مرة إلى نايت شنغهاي،
those big bosses adored her, loved her to death, loved her like a toy motorcycle.
كان هؤلاء الرؤساء الكبار يعشقونها، ويحبونها حتى الموت، ويحبونها مثل دراجة نارية لعبة.
Shut up.
اسكت.
Go home.
اذهب إلى المنزل.
Senior.
كبير.
The way your junior calls you
الطريقة التي يناديك بها صغيرك
feels so affectionate.
أشعر بأنني حنون جدًا.
Wipe it yourself.
امسحها بنفسك.
(Night Shanghai)
(ليلة شنغهاي)
I...
أنا...
Hong.
هونغ.
You're going to kill me.
انت سوف تقتلني
Why are you here, Hong?
لماذا أنت هنا، هونغ؟
I've got something to tell you.
عندي شيء أريد أن أخبرك به.
I heard
لقد سمعت
that batch of arms was safely delivered to the front.
لقد تم تسليم تلك الدفعة من الأسلحة إلى الجبهة بسلام.
Good.
جيد.
Shows that Cao Yu
يظهر أن كاو يو
can still handle things.
لا يزال بإمكاني التعامل مع الأمور.
Here.
هنا.
New mission.
مهمة جديدة.
(Mr. Song, Mr. Yamamoto)
(السيد سونغ، السيد ياماموتو)
♪The world all marvels as fireworks rise♪
♪يندهش العالم كله عندما ترتفع الألعاب النارية♪
♪Magnificent like a blooming dream♪
♪رائعة مثل حلم مزدهر♪
♪Yet who sees the lingering red after the burst♪
♪ومع ذلك من يرى اللون الأحمر المتبقي بعد الانفجار♪
♪Fading into the cold night sky♪
♪تتلاشى في سماء الليل الباردة♪
♪Without the graves of blood and fire♪
♪بدون قبور الدم والنار♪
♪How could there be glory in prosperous times♪
♪كيف يمكن أن يكون هناك مجد في الأوقات المزدهرة♪
♪May that fleeting red of fireworks remain in our hearts♪
♪أتمنى أن يبقى ذلك اللون الأحمر العابر للألعاب النارية في قلوبنا♪
♪Freedom and faith engraved forever♪
♪الحرية والإيمان محفوران إلى الأبد♪
♪You and I are both in the muddy flood♪
♪أنت وأنا في الطوفان الموحل♪
♪Destined to share life and death together♪
♪مُقدَّر لنا أن نتقاسم الحياة والموت معًا♪
♪Life lights the night sky like fireworks' red♪
♪الحياة تضيء سماء الليل مثل الألعاب النارية الحمراء♪
♪Not seeking to engulf the world, just refusing mediocrity♪
♪لا أسعى إلى ابتلاع العالم، فقط أرفض الرداءة♪
♪Even if a single second is all we have in life♪
♪حتى لو كانت ثانية واحدة هي كل ما لدينا في الحياة♪
♪We must sow seeds for our ideals♪
♪علينا أن نزرع بذورًا لمُثُلنا العليا♪